

Jordi Schaefer Ferrer

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Barcelona
(+34) 664-123-742
jschaefer21@gmail.com
github.com/JSchaefer21
www.jschaefer.com
Linkedin.com

Skills

Frontend: React, TypeScript,

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Backend: .NET, SQL Server,

Node JS, MongoDB, APIs

Testing: Jest, Cypress

Others: Git, Agile, Scrum

Languages

Spanish · native

English · B2 (Upper-Intermediate)

German · B1 (Intermediate)

ABOUT ME

Electronic engineer with experience in the automotive industry, currently working as a full-stack developer specializing in React and .NET.

I am detail-oriented and enjoy seeing the evolution of projects and interacting with the code. I consider myself organized with a focus on keeping the code clean and reusable.

EXPERIENCE

FullStack Developer (React / .Net / SQL Server)

Colegio Oficial de Médicos | November 2023 – Present

• Simultaneous management of multiple projects, performing maintenance and adapting them to new requirements.

Design and development of new solutions with a .NET Core backend and React frontends, integrating modern and scalable interfaces.

C# - ASP.NET - Web Forms - MVC - Blazor - .NET Core8 - LINQ - SQL

Frontend Developer (React / TypeScript)

WAGMI venture studio | June 2022 - November 2023 | 1 year 5 months

- Frontend web application development (React and Typescript) for analysis of decentralized Web3 applications and IA's chat customizations.
- Actively participating in the Project from its beginning.
 Context provider Recharts Reactflows Material UI (MUI)

SEAT automotive engineer

Ferchau Engineering | Jun 2017 – November 2021 | 4 years 6 months

- Management and performance of functional, durable and fatigue test for SEAT and AUDI projects.
- Analyze and report testing results, search for solutions and optimizations of parts for release, and homologate the project.

Technical warehouse support at BMW

EDAG Engineering | July 2016 - May 2017 | Munich (Germany) | 1 year

• Management, calibration and maintenance of sensors, cables and electronic components for development testing cars.

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Web Developer

Neoland | April 2022 – Jun 2022

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS, React-Native, NodeJS, MongoDB
- Final project: Web aplication and social media designed for register and share sport activities with data visualization in real time.

CS50 Introduction to Computer Science

Harvard University · edX | February 2022

• C++, Python, SQL

Degree in Electronics and Automatic Control Engineering

Universidad Politécnica de Cataluña | September 2010 – Jun 2016

• Final project: Audio board for Arduino DUE capable of processing high resolution audio data (24bits, 48Khz) in real time.